Odense/Denmark	+45 26 12 54 68
lars@vadgaard.me	
aithub 🖸	in linkedin

SUMMARY _

Highly motivated programmer from Denmark with a great interest in functional programming. Driven, analytic, and eager to learn. Soon-to-be graduate from University of Copenhagen with an M.Sc. in computer science. Teaching assistant in a wide variety of university courses over a six-year period.

EDUCATION _

UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

2015-2018 / Denmark

B.Sc. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

· General profile (programming paradigms, software engineering, algorithms, data science, etc.)

UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

2018-2023 / Denmark

M.Sc. in Computer Science

- · With a slight focus on computation, formal logic, and programming language theory
- Expected graduation in 2023 as break was taken during the degree

EXPERIENCE

UNIVERSITY OF COPENHAGEN

2017-Now / Denmark

TEACHING ASSISTANT IN THE FOLLOWING COURSES:

- LOGIC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE
- IMPLEMENTATION OF PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES
- ADVANCED ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES
- ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES
- COMPUTABILITY AND COMPLEXITY
- PROGRAMMING AND PROBLEM SOLVING

RESPONSIBILITIES:

- ORGANIZING WEEKLY EXERCISE CLASSES
- CODING SOLUTIONS FOR ASSIGNMENTS
- CORRECTING ASSIGNMENTS
- PRE-GRADING EXAMS

PROLOG DEVELOPMENT CENTER (PDC)

2020 / Denmark

STUDENT DEVELOPER

MOSTLY WRITING BATCH SCRIPTS AND SMALL PROLOG FEATURES

DEUTSCHE NACHSCHULE TINGLEFF

2021-2022 / Denmark

TEACHER AT A BOARDING SCHOOL

• TEACHING PHYSICS, CHEMISTRY, AND PROGRAMMING TO YOUNG ADULTS

SKILLS _

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES Experienced: Haskell | Python Familiar: C++ | C# | F# | PHP | JavaScript

KEVROADD I AVOIT

Functional Programming (Haskell, ML, F#, etc.) | Unix/CLI | Full-Stack | Automatization

KEYBOARD LAYOUT Native: Danish Fluent: English | German

RECREATIONAL INTERESTS ____

_____ MISCELLANEOUS ____

- Piano (recent beginner)
- Photography
- Reading

- Preferred Editor: (Neo)VIM
- Keyboard Layout: US International
- · Actual Keyboard: Happy Hacking Keyboard JP

PORTFOLIO/ACHIEVEMENTS _

- Stripped-down version of my B.Sc. thesis with a more recent web interface built on Haskell
- My solution for the final exam in the course Advanced Programming
- · Web app that allows users to buy cryptocurrency regularly and automatically through configurable buy plans
- Developed software for a medical research group that automatically processes data from X-ray scans, saving them hundreds of man-hours